# Thomas Vladeck

I am an ex-entrepreneur with a wide range of experiences and a proven ability to hustle and deliver results. I've started a company, led the development of an international research publication, and successfully negotiated multi-million dollar commodity transactions.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Building Hero**

Cofounder San Francisco, CA December 2011-August 2013

One of two co-founders of Building Hero. Our mission was to apply the state-of-the-art distribution strategies of the solar market to building energy efficiency - starting with LED lighting. Much of our progress was made while I was also working full-time (see below).

- Signed up over 100 clients in San Francisco, New York, Los Angeles, and Atlanta
- Co-wrote Ruby/Rails app to handle in-person sales, billing, and KPI tracking
- Raised project finance fund to finance customer deals
- Closed deals with national brands: Warby Parker and Yogaworks

## **Climate Policy Initiative**

Analyst San Francisco, CA February 2012-April 2013

Led international team of researchers (teams in the US, Germany, Brazil, India and China) in the production of the first compendium of the national and subnational climate policy from major emitting countries. The online version is available at <a href="https://www.thepolicyclimate.org">www.thepolicyclimate.org</a>

- Managed the collection and organization of over 150 datasets from five teams around the world
- Processed data and made prototypes of graphics using the R programming language
- · Managed independent graphic and web designers in the creation of print and online products

## The Palmetto Group

Associate London, UK June 2010-October 2011 Responsible for originating and managing the negotiation of complex, long-term carbon credit transactions between European commodity traders and developing-world project developers under the Clean Development Mechanism.

- Joined firm as the first full-time employee
- Member of 2-3 person deal teams that closed over \$50m worth of transactions
- · Personally originated and successfully closed deals from projects in Haiti, Uganda, and India

#### **EDUCATION**

## **London School of Economics**

MSc, Environmental Policy, 2010 Distinction

- Voted class representative
- Organized speaker series and social events

## Pomona College

BA, Mathematics, 2008 Cum Laude

- · Varsity Baseball Player
- Assisted children with Autism Spectrum Disorder at Casa Colina Rehabilitation Center

# **ABOUT ME**

- Active listener on <u>7 Cups of Tea</u>
- Regular at Mission Cliffs
- Photographer with a Fuji X100
- Blogger at tomvladeck.com
- @tvladeck on Twitter

## **CONTACT INFORMATION**

thomas.vladeck@gmail.com 202.390.0838 2895 Harrison St., San Francisco, CA 94110